<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello Friend</title>
    
    
    
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hello Friend</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 05:52:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Blog With HUGO</title>
      <link>/post/create-blog-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/create-blog-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Before create your blog, make sure you have these steps completed:
  You have Git 2.8 or greater. How To Install Git on Ubuntu 16.04 LTS
  You have a GitHub account. GitHub
  You have HUGO installed. Install HUGO on Debian and Ubuntu
  Create Site or blog to publish. Create a new Site (Add a Theme here, chose wathever you want Hugo Themes)
  Follow these steps to put your website on GitHub  Now it&amp;rsquo;s time to create a repository on GitHub: &amp;lt;USERNAME&amp;gt;.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Filesystem Hierarchy Standard</title>
      <link>/post/the-filesystem-hierarchy-standard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 05:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-filesystem-hierarchy-standard/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          What is a Filesytem Current Linux Structure Directory Some advices  What is a Filesystem A filesystem is the structure of how data is organized in Linux such as boot files, binaries, user´s data, config files, libraries, temp files, etc. A partition with a filesystem is needed in order to store these kind of files.
On Linux there may be more than one partitions on disks using different filesystems. Those filesystems can be found mounted as subdirectories in the directory tree and even can be located either locally or across the network.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 06:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Ismael Garcia Ordoñez  Currently living in Jalisco, Mexico tuxisma@gmail.com Born and raised in Chiapas, Mexico  A motivated, adaptable and responsible computer guy. Self-taught person who is pretty ambitious about learning new stuffs, currently working with Cloud Computing Technologies. In my current job I have automated a lot of things which have saved a lot of time for big processes.
Interests  Python Containers Kubernetes Microservices CI/CD Automation Infrastructure as Code DevSecOps HashiCorp stack  Vault Terraform    Education  Instituto Tecnológico de Tapachula, Chiapas, México.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Java Aplications With Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/post/deploying-java-aplications-with-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 17:04:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/deploying-java-aplications-with-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Three months ago I was learning Docker swarm now I&amp;rsquo;m learning kubernetes as orchestrator this year I&amp;rsquo;m gonna write about k8s a lot so the idea here is show how to deploy Java Aplications within Docker Containers orchestra them with Kubernetes.
When you run containers you always gonna need a orchestrator in order to be more efficient, faster and continuous delivery and so on that&amp;rsquo;s the reason why I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen kubernetes and the true is basically because is the most popular I would say it&amp;rsquo;s so robust, ambicious, fault-tolerance, scaling, discovery abilities and why not use it, mainly was created at Google and now is hosted by the Cloud Native Computing Foundation(CNCF).
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/archive/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>