<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ismael Garcia</title>
    
    
    
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ismael Garcia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 03:39:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure as Code - Terraform</title>
      <link>/post/infrastructure-as-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 03:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/infrastructure-as-code/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          What is Infrastructure as code Why is so important What is Terraform Features of terraform Use Cases  What is Infrastructure as code Infrastructure as code (IaC) is a way of how you define the resources that you want to deploy as code. IaC helps to build, change, version your infrastructure at low-level (Compute instances, storage, networking) and high-level(DNS entries, SaaS features).
Why is so important The traditional way of provision a compute instance is via Ticket services such as Service Now, so the user raises a ticket and then the sys admin takes that ticket and provision that compute instance through a GUI Service or maybe using the CLI, so what about if the user needs thousand of compute instances ?
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Filesystem Hierarchy Standard</title>
      <link>/post/the-filesystem-hierarchy-standard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 05:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-filesystem-hierarchy-standard/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          What is a Filesytem Current Linux Structure Directory Things to consider  What is a Filesystem A filesystem is the structure of how data is organized in Linux such as boot files, binaries, user´s data, config files, libraries, temp files, etc. A partition with a filesystem is needed in order to store these kind of files.
On Linux there may be more than one partitions on disks using different filesystems.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Blog With HUGO</title>
      <link>/post/create-blog-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:04:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/create-blog-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Before create your blog, make sure you have these steps completed:
  You have Git 2.8 or greater. How To Install Git on Ubuntu 16.04 LTS
  You have a GitHub account. GitHub
  You have HUGO installed. Install HUGO on Debian and Ubuntu
  Create Site or blog to publish. Create a new Site (Add a Theme here, chose wathever you want Hugo Themes)
  Follow these steps to put your website on GitHub  Now it&amp;rsquo;s time to create a repository on GitHub: &amp;lt;USERNAME&amp;gt;.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Java Aplications With Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/post/deploying-java-aplications-with-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 17:04:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/deploying-java-aplications-with-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Three months ago I was learning Docker swarm now I&amp;rsquo;m learning kubernetes as orchestrator this year I&amp;rsquo;m gonna write about k8s a lot so the idea here is show how to deploy Java Aplications within Docker Containers orchestra them with Kubernetes.
When you run containers you always gonna need a orchestrator in order to be more efficient, faster and continuous delivery and so on that&amp;rsquo;s the reason why I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen kubernetes and the true is basically because is the most popular I would say it&amp;rsquo;s so robust, ambicious, fault-tolerance, scaling, discovery abilities and why not use it, mainly was created at Google and now is hosted by the Cloud Native Computing Foundation(CNCF).
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>