<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Welcome aboard!</title>
    <link>https://tuxisma.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Welcome aboard!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>copyright</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 01:31:21 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tuxisma.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Blog With HUGO</title>
      <link>https://tuxisma.github.io/post/create-blog-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tuxisma.github.io/post/create-blog-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Before create your blog, make sure you have these steps completed:
 You have Git 2.8 or greater. How To Install Git on Ubuntu 16.04 LTS
 You have a GitHub account. GitHub
 You have HUGO installed. Install HUGO on Debian and Ubuntu
 Create Site or blog to publish. Create a new Site (Add a Theme here, chose wathever you want Hugo Themes)
  Follow these steps to put your website on GitHub  Now it&amp;rsquo;s time to create a repository on GitHub: &amp;lt;USERNAME&amp;gt;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m back!</title>
      <link>https://tuxisma.github.io/post/im-back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 01:31:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tuxisma.github.io/post/im-back-again/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back again and I&amp;rsquo;m thinking to write some good topics here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Java Aplications With Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://tuxisma.github.io/post/deploying-java-aplications-with-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 17:04:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tuxisma.github.io/post/deploying-java-aplications-with-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Three months ago I was learning Docker swarm now I&amp;rsquo;m learning kubernetes as orchestrator this year I&amp;rsquo;m gonna write about k8s a lot so the idea here is show how to deploy Java Aplications within Docker Containers orchestra them with Kubernetes.
When you run containers you always gonna need a orchestrator in order to be more efficient, faster and continuous delivery and so on that&amp;rsquo;s the reason why I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen kubernetes and the true is basically because is the most popular I would say it&amp;rsquo;s so robust, ambicious, fault-tolerance, scaling, discovery abilities and why not use it, mainly was created at Google and now is hosted by the Cloud Native Computing Foundation(CNCF).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missandei is here</title>
      <link>https://tuxisma.github.io/post/missandei-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 17:04:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tuxisma.github.io/post/missandei-is-here/</guid>
      <description>Jan 5, 2018 by Ismael Garcia
I am really excited because my lady is here, yeah my laptop baptized as “Missandei” I was looking forward to get my precious, well let me tell you her features and what OS I have installed:
 Memory 12 GiB
 Processor Intel Core i7-350M CPU @2.90GHz x 4
 OS Type 64-bit CentOS 7
 Graphics Intel lvybridge Mobile i
 GNOME</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Ismael Garcia&#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://tuxisma.github.io/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 14:05:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tuxisma.github.io/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Hello there! I&amp;rsquo;m starting almost a new year and I decided to post some articles here in github so the idea is include content about Cloud Computing and some things about my SysAdmin life also I wanna post some articles about one of my favorite hobbies (Hiking). And another hand I wanna say thank you for all the good and bad things that come to me this year, especially starting a new year thinking different, I wanna say thank you to my Sensei Francisco Moctezuma for support me and teach me a bunch of stuff about Cloud Computing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>